想在此处添加您的广告信息？立即联系 www.OpenSubtitles.org
-=圣城家园SCG字幕组 http://hdscg.com/=-
仅供翻译交流使用, 禁止用于商业用途
协调: 影子
翻译: 阿bon 熊熊 霹雳旋风猪 波特妹子
校对: UUUUUU
花生漫画大电影
原著舒尔茨
啊 贝多芬
Ah, Beethoven.
莱纳斯 该起床啦
Linus, time to get up.
你可不想上学迟到吧
You don't want to be late for school.
- 起床!  - 啊!
- Get up!  - Ah!
我的毯子!
My blanket!
喂?
Hello?
下雪了?
Snow day?
下雪啦!
Snow day!
今天不用上学!
No school today!
美梦成真啦!
Dreams do come true!
不用上学!
No school!
富兰克林和薄荷·派蒂来我这一队!
Franklin and Peppermint Patty are on my team!
- 我拿了曲棍球棍!  - 我拿了冰鞋!
- I got my hockey stick!  - I got my skates!
谁有冰球?
Who has the pucks?
今天看起来不错哟 乒乓
Looking sharp today, Pigpen.
抱歉来迟了
Sorry I'm late.
他怎么那么磨蹭?
Ew! What's taking him so long?
快点 查理·布朗!
Come on, Charlie Brown!
不 还不行 就这件!
No. Not quite. That's the one!
诶哟!
Whoa!
我拿了风筝!
I've got my kite!
就是今天了 我感受到了!
Today's the day. I can feel it!
风筝? 今天放?
A kite? Today?
在大冬天的?
In the middle of winter?
来吧 小伙伴们!
Come on, guys!
只有查理·布朗干得出来
Only Charlie Brown.
一个新风筝 一阵刚好的轻风
A new kite, a perfect breeze.
一切都如此完美
It all feels just right.
既然吃风筝的树已经冬眠
Now that the Kite-Eating Tree is sleeping for the winter...
我们就没什么好怕啦
we have nothing to fear.
起飞!
Lift off!
等一下
Wait a minute.
它升空啦 它在飞! 伙伴们!
It's in the air. It's flying! Hey, guys!
快看 看呐 我做到了!
Look! Look, I did it!
嘿 查理·布朗
Hey, Charlie Brown.
还是这么倒霉 是吧?
Still no luck, huh?
记住 继续下去的勇气
Remember, it's the courage
才是重要的! 哎哟!
to continue that counts! Whoa!
风筝失控啦!
Runaway kite!
抱歉!
Sorry!
它停不下来了!
No brakes!
现在轮到我的阿克塞尔三周跳了
And now, for my famous triple Axel!
震惊吧!
Prepare to be amazed!
天哪!
Ooh!
四周跳! 好棒!
A quadruple! Bravo!
可恶的吃风筝树
Stupid Kite-Eating Tree.
真要命
Good grief.
你这木鱼脑袋!
You blockhead!
我早该知道
I should have known.
什么人才会想在大冬天
What kind of a person tries to fly a kite
放风筝呢?
in the middle of winter?
你怎么都不会放弃的?
Don't you ever know when to give up?
你的风筝永远也飞不上天的
You will never get that kite to fly.
为什么? 因为你是查理·布朗!
Why? Because you're Charlie Brown!
谢谢 莱纳斯
Thanks, Linus.
听着 查理·布朗
Listen, Charlie Brown.
就是因为不听我姐姐露西那些话
Ignoring what my sister Lucy says
我才走得到今天
has enabled me to make it this far in life.
要是没有像你这样的好朋友我该怎么办呢?
What would I do without a good friend like you?
哇哈!
Whoa!
哇哦!
天哪 我的小可爱!
Aw, my Sweet Babboo!
他咋能这么可爱?
Isn't he the cutest thing?
小心 伙计!
Careful, sir!
别碰我的卷发!
Watch the curls!
我才不管露西说什么
I don't care what Lucy says.
也许过去我风筝放的很糟糕...
I may have had troubles in the past flying a kite...
也许我从没赢过一场棒球比赛...
and I may have never won a baseball game...
但是爱拼才会赢
but it's not for the lack of trying.
只要我日复一日到土墩上投球
My pitching has to improve
我的投球技术一定会进步
if I come out here to my trusty mound every day.
查理·布朗永不言弃
Charlie Brown is not a quitter.
九局下半 两人出局
Bottom of the 9th. Two outs.
（棒球比赛挽回局势的最后的机会 意味着主队暂时平局或落后）
三振出局就能成就一个英雄投手
A strike-out here would make the pitcher an instant hero.
（三振出局：投手通过投球使击球员三击不中而出局的防守行为）
成败在此一投
It all comes down to this one pitch.
让我看看你能否招架我的快球
Let's see if you can handle my fastball.
一号 快速直球
Ol' Number One. The Heater.
布朗号子弹
The Brown Bullet.
哇哈哈!
Woo-hoo!
啊?
Hmm?
注定是个难度过的冬天
It's going to be a long winter.
有人要搬到
Someone's moving in
我家街对面了吗?
across the street from me?
伙伴们 看! 有新伙伴要搬过来啦!
Hey, gang, look! There's a new kid moving in!
大哥哥 淡定!
Big brother, pull yourself together!
快来 查理·布朗!
Come on, Charlie Brown!
- 让开!  - 伙伴们
- Get out of the way!  - Hey, guys.
你们看到什么了? 谁来了?
What do you see? Who is it?
我好像看到一架钢琴! 希望他也喜欢贝多芬!
Oh, I think I see a piano! I hope he loves Beethoven!
贝多芬 傻多芬
Beethoven, Schmeethoven.
也许他能欣赏我的天生丽质
Maybe he will appreciate my natural beauty.
谁会在意那个?
Who cares about that?
只要他是个比玛茜好的守门员就行
As long as he's a better goalie than Marcie.
你伤到我了 先生
You're hurting me, sir.
抱歉 但我是说实话
I'm sorry, but it's true.
不 我是说你扯到我头发了!
No, you're pulling on my hair!
我只希望他对南瓜大王
I just hope he'll have an open mind
没什么偏见
about the Great Pumpkin.
（莱纳斯每个万圣夜都会在南瓜地里等待南瓜大王的降临 因此被小伙伴们嘲笑）
好像他们有一个面包机!
I think they have a toaster!
我只愿这个新来的没听说过我
I just hope this new kid has never heard of me.
这样他就对我过去的种种不顺一无所知
He would know nothing of my past imperfections.
改过自新的机会
It's not often you get the opportunity
可不常有
to start over with a clean slate.
这一次 一切将会不同
This time, things will be different.
哇哦!
Whoa!
是他干的!
He did it!
史努比...
Snoopy...
为什么我每次的努力都事与愿违?
why is it that everything I try turns out wrong?
有时我想小伙伴们是不是真的喜欢我
Sometimes I wonder if the kids really like me.
也许那个新朋友会看到真正的我 就像你看到的
Maybe that new kid will see me for who I really am, like you.
狗狗不会试图左右或评价你
A dog doesn't try to give advice or judge you.
他们爱的只是纯粹的你
They just love you for who you are.
能有一个静静坐在身边
It's nice to have someone
听你说话的伙伴真好
that will just sit and listen to you.
人类最好的朋友
Man's best friend.
你可上不了学 史努比
You can't come to school, Snoopy.
当只乖乖狗回家吧
Now be a good dog and go home.
啊哈
Hmm.
狗狗不得入内!
No dogs allowed!
我好像看到新伙伴了
I think I saw the new kid.
你看到那个搬家车来了吗?
Did you see that moving truck arrive?
你觉得会是谁呢?
Who do you suppose it will be?
新孩子来啦!
The new kid is coming!
那可不是新来的
That's not the new kid.
嘿 查理·布朗
Hey, Charlie Brown.
早上好 莱纳斯 你拿着什么呢?
Good morning, Linus. What do you have there?
轮到我上台讲故事啦
It's my turn for show and tell today.
这个是飞行员里奇特霍芬同款飞机
This is the same plane flown by Manfred von Richthofen.
- 谁?  - 红男爵
- Who?  - The Red Baron.
(德国 "红男爵" 曼弗雷德.冯.里奇特霍芬在第一次世界大战中
共击落80架飞机 位居德国飞行员之首 同时也是一战中世界王牌的第一位)
世界大战中最有名的飞行员
The most famous aviator during The Great War.
这是假的吧 是吗?
It's not real, is it?
啊! 我的天然小卷卷!
Aah! My naturally curly hair!
快躲 莱纳斯! 啊呜!
Duck, Linus! Whoa!
哎呀!
Yikes!
好的 奥兹玛老师
Yes, Miss Othmar.
先生?
Sir?
先生
Sir.
先生!
Sir!
二! 不 三!
Two! No, three!
大概猜到了?
Was I close?
还没开始上课呢 先生
Class hasn't started yet, sir.
什么? 新孩子要来我们班了
What? The new kid is joining our class.
她看上去不太像个守门员
She doesn't look like a goalie to me.
天哪! 她好漂亮
Wow! She's pretty.
她才没那么漂亮
She's not that pretty.
莱纳斯 她看了我一眼！
Linus.  She looked at me!
啊 不会又是年度标准化考试吧!
Aww, not the yearly standardized test again!
老师 这个考试
Ma'am, will this test
能准确的反应我们在这学到的东西吗?
accurately reflect the knowledge we have gained here?
我们在这么小的年纪就...公平吗
Is it fair we, at this young age...
好的 老师
Yes, ma'am.
谢谢
Thanks.
第一题
Question 1.
"如果你有六个红番茄..."
"If you had 6 red tomatoes and..."
啊...
Aw...
红色
Red.
拜托 专心点
Come on, focus.
第一印象是一切
First impressions are everything.
狗狗勿入!
No dogs!
啊呜
Hmm.
做完了?
Already done?
她一定很聪明
She must be smart.
啊?
Huh?
上面有牙印
It's got teeth marks.
她跟我一样都喜欢咬铅笔耶
She nibbles on her pencil like I do.
我们有共同点耶!
We have something in common!
只剩一分钟了?
One minute left?
别挡道 查克!
Out of my way, Chuck!
写名字? 好的 老师
Write our names? Yes, ma'am.
查克 你是想偷摸我的手吗?
Chuck, are you trying to hold my hand?
你这个小滑头
You sly dog.
哇!
Ooh!
你好 我是布朗查理
Uh, hi, I'm Brown Charlie.
我是说 "不理查朗."
I mean, "Barnie Clown."
我是说...
I mean...
你来看什么病?
What are you in for?
你有过笑的停不下来的感觉吗?
Have you ever had that feeling when you can't stop smiling?
啥?
Huh?
心脏在胸膛里砰砰跳?
Your heart pounds inside your chest?
你想站起来但是膝盖却软了?
You try to stand but your knees become weak?
然后那个红发小女孩
And then that Little Red-Haired Girl
看了你一眼 哇!
glances at you. Whoa!
然后生活一切的可能性
And all of life's possibilities
都变得如此清晰
become so clear.
但接着你就意识到...
And then you realize...
她根本不知道你的存在
she has no idea you're alive.
我为什么来这儿?
Why am I here?
因为我患上了
Because I just came down
严重的失败综合症
with a serious case of inadequacy.
她来了
Here she comes.
我留个好印象的机会来了
This is my chance to make a good impression.
还是明天好了
Maybe tomorrow.
这是一个风雨交加的黑夜
It was a dark and stormy night.
在法国乡村的上空...
High above the French countryside...
第一次世界大战的王牌飞行员...
the World War I Flying Ace had never been so close...
和他一生的敌人从未如此接近...
to his lifelong enemy...
臭名昭著的红爵士
the infamous Red Baron.
嘘
Shh.
关键点在于不让她发现
The key is keeping a low profile.
现在 我们只需要保持距离
For now, we just keep our distance.
啊! 史努比!
Ahh! Snoopy!
不!
No!
嗷!
Oh!
唷!
Phew!
差一点
That was a close one.
只要我可以鼓起勇气过去 我就会...
If I could only work up the nerve to go over there, I'd...
你在看什么 大哥哥?
What are you looking at, big brother?
你疯了吗? 啊?
Are you crazy? Huh?
啊哦
Oh.
你坠入爱河了!
You're in love!
第一章
Chapter 1.
这是史上最美妙的爱情故事
It was the greatest love story ever told.
她的名字叫菲菲
Her name was Fifi.
她是他心中
She was the most beautiful thing
最美的存在
he had ever seen.
呸!
Yuck!
真不敢相信
I can't believe I'm about to talk
我就要和红发小女孩说话了
to the Little Red-Haired Girl.
这种时刻最需要
It's moments like this
挚友在旁了
when you need your faithful friend.
好啦
Yep.
如果这种时刻你要选择一个人
If there's one person you want by your side
在你身边的话...
at a moment like this...
一定是你忠实的狗狗
it's your loyal dog.
你好?
Hello?
你好? 哼
Hello? Hmm.
她说 "你好"！
She said, "Hello"!
查理·布朗!
Charlie Brown!
太阳都快落山了你来这里干嘛?
What brings you out here so late in the day?
给我点女孩方面的建议吧 露西
I need your advice on girls, Lucy.
你自己就是女孩 对不?
You're a girl, right?
现在有一个我想要留下好印象的女生
Let's just say there's this girl I'd like to impress.
但是她是个人物 而我并不是
But she's something and I'm nothing.
如果是我是个人物 而她并不是
If I were something and she was nothing,
我就能跟她说话了
I could talk to her.
或者 如果我们俩都不咋地
Or, if she was nothing and I was nothing,
我也能跟她说话
I could talk to her.
但现在是她很厉害而我什么都不是
But she's something and I'm nothing,
所以我对她开不了口
so I just can't talk to her.
你真可笑 查理·布朗
You're being ridiculous, Charlie Brown.
你也有很多优点
You have much to offer.
她有个漂亮的脸蛋
She has a pretty face
漂亮的让我很紧张
and pretty faces make me nervous.
漂亮脸蛋? 漂亮脸蛋?
Pretty face? Pretty face?
我也有漂亮脸蛋!
I have a pretty face!
我的脸怎么没让你紧张?
How come my face doesn't make you nervous?
你怎么就敢跟我说话 查理·布朗?
How come you can talk to me, Charlie Brown?
我想知道俘获她的心的秘诀
I just need to know the secret to winning her heart.
瞅瞅镜子 查理·布朗
Look into this mirror, Charlie Brown.
这就是注定失败的脸 典型的悲剧脸
This is the face of failure. A classic failure face.
你觉得女孩子喜欢失败者吗 查理·布朗?
Do you think girls like failures, Charlie Brown?
这 不
Well, no.
女孩们喜欢有成就的人
Girls want someone with proven success.
你获得过什么奖项吗?
Have you won any awards?
比如国会荣誉勋章?
Like a Congressional Medal of Honor?
或者诺贝尔和平奖?
Or a Nobel Peace Prize?
你有什么房地产持有股份吗?
What are your real estate holdings?
你有多方面的才能吗?
Do you have a diversified portfolio?
啥?
Huh?
让我告诉你这个小秘密吧 查理·布朗
Let me let you in on a little secret, Charlie Brown.
如果你真的想给姑娘们留下深刻印象
If you really want to impress girls,
你要向她们展现出成功人士的样子
you need to show them you're a winner.
成功人士? 我?
A winner? Me?
露西 你说的有道理
Lucy, you may be on to something.
当然 当我说"你"
Of course, when I say "you,"
你知道我不是指你
you know I don't mean you personally.
请付5美分
That will be five cents, please.
叮咚 叮咚 叮咚 多好听的声音呀
Nickels, nickels, nickels. What a beautiful sound.
"祝贺你 你踏出了走向成功
"Congratulations. You're now on your way
的第一步"
to becoming a winner."
"一 忘记你对自己的所有认知"
"Step 1. Forget everything you ever knew about yourself."
嗯
Hmm.
好的 "第二步
Okay. "Step 2.
树立自信"
Project confidence."
"站得笔直"
"Don't slouch."
"时刻直视对方的目光"
"Maintain eye contact at all times."
呀哈!
Yeehaw!
驾 我的小马!
Giddy-up, little pony!
呀哈!
Yeehaw!
你在干什么?
What are you doing?
我准备参加一个大型才艺表演
I'm going to be a rodeo star in the big talent show.
等我赢到了一等奖的绶带...
When I win that first-prize ribbon...
所有人都会知道我的名字...
there will be no one who hasn't heard the name...
萨莉·布朗和她可靠的马 扫把柄!
Sally Brown and her trusty horse, Broomstick!
赢得才艺表演 是个好主意
Win the talent show. Now that's a great idea.
露西说的就是这个意思
This is just what Lucy was talking about.
哈哈!
Ha-ha!
哒哒!
Ta-da!
哈!
Ha!
哈哈!
Ha-ha!
我们准备好了
We're ready.
哇! 看那个
Whoa! Look at that.
那是查理·布朗么?
Is that Charlie Brown?
哇!
Whoa!
她在那
She's here.
我有种很好的预感
I have a really good feeling that tonight
今晚她会看到全新的查理·布朗
she will see the new Charlie Brown.
居然是查理·布朗?
Charlie Brown?
作为你的心理医生 我很惊讶看到你来这里
As your psychiatrist, I'm surprised to see you here.
像你这样缺乏安全感的人
A person with all your insecurities
一般不会来参加才艺表演
normally wouldn't enter a talent show.
我...
I'm...
我要揍你!
I ought to slug you!
啊! 我被狗亲了! 我染上了狗细菌!
Ugh! I've been kissed by a dog! I have dog germs!
热水! 消毒剂!
Get hot water! Get some disinfectant!
拿碘酒来!
Get some iodine!
我们快开始吧 不要浪费时间了
Let's keep this thing moving. Time's a-wasting.
谢谢!
Thank you!
祝你好运 查克!
Break a leg, Chuck!
对你的助手好点 查理
Treat your assistant kindly, Charles.
好了萨莉 我们时间不多了
Okay, Sally, we're running behind,
小马步跑起来 快点!
so gallop, don't trot!
大家把掌声留到最后
Save the applause for the end, everyone.
如果大家喜欢 我还有回场呢!
If you like this, wait for the encore!
你妹妹的节目太没趣了
Your sister is really dying out there.
喂 那不是一匹真马!
Hey, that's not a real horse!
对不起了 查理·布朗 大家都受够了
Sorry, Charlie Brown. This has gone on long enough.
拉上大幕!
Drop the curtain!
别这样 她说她准备了一个超棒的收场
Don't do that. She said she has a big finish.
这么说吧 要么你演要么她演
Well, it's either your act or hers.
我们不能一直这么等着
We can't hold forever.
史努比 计划有变
Change of plans, Snoopy.
哇
Wow.
哞
Moo.
大哥哥?
Big brother?
用绳子套我
Rope me.
- 哞  - 那不是个真的奶牛
- Moo.  - That's not a real cow.
我会抓到你的!
I'm gonna get you!
哇哦!
Woo-hoo!
嗨...哈!
Hi... Hi-ya!
对不起 先生
Sorry, sir.
做的好
Good one.
哦 施罗德...
Oh, Schroeder...
哇-哦!
Woo-hoo!
你可以跑 小东西 但你藏不住的!
You can run, little dogie, but you can't hide!
这太棒了! 哈!
This is going great! Yee-haw!
我的名字叫卡拉米蒂萨莉...
My name is Calamity Sally...
是这个镇子上
the best bronc-busting,
套牛手艺最好的牛仔女孩!
lasso-roping cowgirl in this here town!
谢谢你 大哥哥
Thanks, big brother.
哇 哇!
Whoa, whoa!
"哞"?
"Moo"?
反正也没有人看校报
Nobody reads the school paper anyhow.
往好处想吧 查理·布朗
Look on the bright side, Charlie Brown.
出名总不是坏事
They say there's no such thing as bad publicity.
你说的对 莱纳斯
You're right, Linus.
她现在肯定知道我是谁了
She definitely knows who I am now.
其实 查理·布朗 如果你那么喜欢她...
You know, Charlie Brown, if you like her so much...
为什么不直接去找她跟她做个自我介绍?
why not just walk up to her and introduce yourself?
在我昨天晚上
After the complete fool
出了那么大的洋相之后?
I made out of myself last night?
好啊 我还不如上天呢?
Yeah, and why don't I just fly to the moon?
天哪 她在跟他们说话?
Oh, brother. She's talking to them?
这下没法重新做人了
So much for a fresh start.
要没有时间了
Time is running out.
"第六步
"Number 6.
告诉你自己 "我当之无愧 我能做到"
Tell yourself, 'l am worthy. I can do this."
"我具备一切需要的素质"
"'I have what it takes.'"
喂?
Hello?
是你女朋友打来的
Your girlfriend's on the phone.
- 喂?  - 嗨 查克
- Hello?  - Hey, Chuck.
我是薄荷·派蒂
This is Peppermint Patty.
- 你最近怎么样?  - 嗯 我...
- How have you been?  - Well, I...
听着 我有好消息给你 查克
Listen, I have some great news for you, Chuck.
冬季舞会马上就到了...
The Winter Dance is in a few weeks...
我准备跟你跳一支舞
and I'm saving a dance for you.
毕竟 玛茜要我负责管理
Anyway, Marcie put me in charge
点心委员会
of the refreshment committee.
我帮你安排了
I took it upon myself
让你负责做杯子蛋糕
and signed you up to make the cupcakes.
你干了什么? 我不会做杯子蛋糕
You did what? I can't cook cupcakes.
我只会做吐司
The only thing I do know how to make is toast.
而且 我根本就不想去冬季舞会?
Besides, why would I even want to go to the Winter Dance?
吐司和杯子蛋糕! 听起来很不错 查克
Toast and cupcakes! That sounds good, Chuck.
到时候见
See you there.
等一下 我是说...
Hold on. I said...
喂?喂?
Hello? Hello?
简直糟透了
Rats.
嗨! 你在干什么?
Hey! What's going on?
小点声!
Turn it down!
快调小点声!
Turn it down in there!
啊?
Huh?
她喜欢跳舞
She likes to dance.
哎
Ugh.
嗯?
Hmm?
一 二 三 四
One, two, three, four.
哇哦!
Whew!
要有个舞伴就好了
I could really use a dance partner.
祝你好运
Good luck with that.
一 二 三 四
One, two, three, four.
好了 史努比 我已经把基本的东西掌握了
Okay, Snoopy, I got the basics down.
但是如果我想赢 我还得再下点功夫
But if I'm going to win, I need to step it up.
一 二 三 四
One, two, three, four.
我已经能想象了
I can see it now.
胜利者已产生!
We have our winners!
让我们用掌声欢迎掌声
Let us applaud them
他们按传统来跳一支冠军舞!
as they begin the traditional dance of the champions!
史努比!
Snoopy!
谢谢你的帮助
Thanks for the help.
我在你的食盆里留了点曲奇饼干
I left some cookies in your dog dish.
一 二 三 四
One, two, three, four.
一 二 三...
One, two, three...
我一直想和乒乓跳舞
You know, I've always wanted to dance with Pigpen.
啊! 恶心!
Ugh! Yuck!
为什么没人跳舞呢? 这不是个舞会么
Why isn't anyone dancing? It's called a dance.
哦 我的小可爱!
Oh, Sweet Babboo!
哦 不 她来了!
Oh, no, here she comes!
总有人要开场的
Someone needs to get this dance started.
不!
No!
如果让我自己来说的话
These cupcakes don't look half bad,
这些杯子蛋糕看起来还可以
if I do say so myself.
这次我完全准备好了
This time I've come totally prepared.
如果没有你我不可能办成的
I couldn't have done it without you.
从前的查理·布朗还是会躺在床上
The old Charlie Brown would still be lying in bed
装胃疼
with a stomachache.
哈?
Huh?
真要命
Good grief.
玛茜 看! 大家都在这了!
Marcie, look! Everyone's here!
哦 让我帮你拿吧 玛茜
Oh. Let me help you with that, Marcie.
你真是个绅士 查理
Such a gentleman, Charles.
她来了
She's here.
嗯?
Huh?
好了 女士们
Okay, ladies.
该是你们展现最好的舞姿的时候了
It's time for you to show off your best move.
你们中的谁会赢得我们
Which one of you will win the first half
的舞蹈比赛最佳的舞伴...
of our dance competition...
并把奖杯带回家?
and take home the trophy?
让我们拭目以待!
Let them hear it!
跳得真好
Nice moves.
耶 耶 耶 耶 耶 耶!
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah!
听听这欢呼声!
Listen to that noise!
我觉得可以说冠军已经揭晓!
I think it's safe to say we know who our winner is!
她赢了
She won.
现在 轮到小伙子们了...
And now, it's the gentlemen's turn...
看看谁来和我们获胜的女士一起...
to see who will be joining our lovely winning lady...
跳今晚的最后一场舞
for the final dance of the night.
我得过去
I got to get out there.
你们都准备好了么? 我们要开始了!
Are you guys ready? Then here we go!
就是现在了
This is it.
机会就是现在
It's now or never.
哇!
Whoa!
看看那个长的有趣的孩子的舞步
Check out the moves on that funny-looking kid
鼻子特别大的那个
with the big nose!
耶! 太棒了!
Yeah! All right!
好了 就像你练习时的那样
Okay, just like you practiced.
记住舞步
Remember the steps.
一 二 三 四
One, two, three, four.
一 二 三...
One, two, three...
- 查理·布朗?  - 不错嘛!
- Charlie Brown?  - All right!
看来我们也许产生了冠军!
It looks like we may have a winner here!
马上就成了
It's going to happen.
我就要和那个红头发的姑娘跳舞了
I'm about to dance with the Little Red-Haired Girl.
哇!
Whoa!
我们快从这出去!
Let's get out of here!
我认识你么?
Do I know you?
等等! 还没结束呢
Wait! It's not over yet.
谢谢 老兄
Thanks, buddy.
我不想说 史努比...
I hate to say it, Snoopy...
感觉好像我越是努力
it seems like the harder I try,
她就离我越遥远
the further away she gets.
王牌飞行员在空中飞着
The Flying Ace took to the skies.
他无休无止地寻找着那个偷走了他的心的姑娘
He searched endlessly for the girl who had stolen his heart.
白日梦不会成真的 查理·布朗
Daydreaming will not make her materialize, Charlie Brown.
- 她不在这  - 白日梦 我么?
- She's not here.  - Daydreaming? Me?
她星期一会回来的
She'll be back on Monday.
我听说她回了东边去照顾
I heard she went back east to take care
她的祖母了 她祖母病了
of her grandmother, who isn't feeling well.
她看起来像是那种
She seems like the kind of person
会做那种事的人
who would do that sort of thing.
哦! 不会又是一份读书笔记吧!
Aww! Not another book report!
该选搭档了
Time to pick our partners.
不要男孩 不要男孩
No boys. No boys.
拜托...
Please...
帕蒂! 太棒了!
Patty! Yes!
太好了!
All right!
不 啊哈
Nope. Uh-uh.
就这个了
Yes.
施罗德!
Schroeder!
没什么好否认的 都写在卡片上了
There's no denying it. It was written in the cards.
红头发的姑娘 今天真是幸运的一天!
The Little Red-Haired Girl. My lucky day!
这能改变一切 她会看见一个新的我的
This changes everything. She will see the new me.
我们可以一起赢得奖杯!
And together we will win the gold star!
在那之后 什么事情都有可能!
After that, anything is possible!
我们可能是第一个登月的孩子!
We could be the first kids to land on the moon!
孩子们小小的一步...
One small step for kids...
对查理·布朗来说是一大步
one giant leap for Charlie Brown.
你要帮我 莱纳斯
You've got to help me, Linus.
和红头发女孩做搭档
I'm not sure I can handle being partners
我不知道我自己行不行
with the Little Red-Haired Girl.
我得慢慢来
I need to slow things down.
也许我还没准备好开始一段认真的感情
Maybe I'm not ready for a serious relationship.
我供养的起她么?
How will I support her?
我付不起抵押贷款 如果我用第三方保管账户呢?
I can't afford a mortgage. What if I'm put into escrow?
查理·布朗 你太荒唐了
Charlie Brown, you're being ridiculous.
我认识的所有人里只有你
You're the only person I know
会把一个简简单单的读书笔记...
who can turn a simple book report...
变成一个终身的契约
into a lifelong commitment.
我以前从没有过这么大的担当
I've never been responsible for anything before.
搞砸的话 她的天是不是要塌了!
This could be the worst thing that's ever happened to her!
莱纳斯 我只是突然发现
Linus, it just hit me.
我知道怎么去做她的英雄了
I think I know how to become her hero.
当她去照顾她祖母的时候...
While she's away taking care of her grandmother...
我独自完成我们俩的读书汇报
I could complete the book report for the two of us.
这样也行 但是如果你想听我的建议...
That's one way to go, but if you want my advice...
他们在公布考试成绩 快过来
They're posting the test scores. Come on.
看哪 有人拿了满分 先生
Look. Someone got a perfect score, sir.
天才才能拿满分呢
You would have to be a genius to get a perfect score.
我还以为满分是不可能的呢
I didn't know that was even possible.
是他! 他来了!
It's him! Here he comes!
之前谁都没得过100分
No one in the world has ever gotten 100 before.
满分?
A perfect score?
我么? 搞错了吧
Me? This can't be right.
不 查理·布朗 看
No, Charlie Brown, look.
你真的得了满分
You really do have a perfect score.
我听说花生酱对大脑有营养
I have heard peanut butter is brain food.
干的好 查克 好孩子
Nice job, Chuck, old boy.
我一直知道你是有潜力的 查理
I always knew you had it in you, Charles.
一定搞错了!
This can't be right!
让开!
Out of my way!
完美先生 查理·布朗?
Mr. Perfect, Charlie Brown?
一定是印错了!
It must be a typo!
我不相信 我不会相信的!
I don't believe it. I won't believe it!
我要求重新核算!
I demand a recount!
中午好 同学们和教职员工们
Good afternoon, students and staff.
我们有件事要特别宣布
We have a special announcement.
周一的早晨将有全校大会...
There will be an all-school assembly Monday morning...
来庆祝我们杰出的同学 查理·布朗...
to celebrate our illustrious classmate, Charlie Brown...
在标准化考试中获得了完美的成绩
who achieved a perfect score on the standardized test.
让下道 天才驾到
Make way. Genius coming through!
我下周有个科学作业要交
I have a science project due next week.
你能给我点意见么?
Can you give me your thoughts?
嗨 我先看到他的!
Hey, I saw him first!
他们说你是天才 你会读心么?
They say you're a genius. Can you read my mind?
嗨 别围着他了!
Hey, leave him alone!
对呀 别围着他!
Yeah, leave him alone!
查理·布朗 要写读书报告的话
Now, Charlie Brown, as far as the book report goes,
你推荐哪本书?
what would you suggest?
如果你紧跟经典
Well, you can never go wrong
就永远不会出错
if you stick with the classics.
漫画书?
A comic book?
我还以为经典的作品都得是硬皮书
I thought classics had to have hard covers.
听听我们说的这蠢话
Boy, do we feel stupid now.
看看 多么现代的作品
Will you look at this. What a contemporary piece.
注意他对空间的运用
Notice his use of space.
你们都疯了么?
Have you all lost your minds?
哇
Wow.
你们得了所谓的"非理性恐惧症"
You have what is referred to as an "irrational fear."
哈?
Huh?
喂 小屁孩! 你在干吗?
Hey, kid! What do you think you're doing?
跟随伟人的脚步啊
Following in the footsteps of greatness.
突击!
Breakaway!
射门 查理·布朗 射啊!
Shoot it, Charlie Brown! Shoot it!
角度太刁钻了 查理
Nice use of angles there, Charles.
干的漂亮 查理·布朗!
All right, Charlie Brown!
嗯
Hmm.
没有光圣诞老人要怎么找到我们的房子啊?
But how is Santa ever going to find our house without lights?
耶!
Yay!
就从这里开始
And this is where it all began.
作为一个年轻人 他花了很长时间
As a youth, he passed many hours
坐在那张椅子上...
just sitting in that chair...
独自沉思
keeping his deep thoughts to himself.
这里我们看到的是他早期
And here we have his early kites,
- 用于空气动力学研究的风筝  - 哇
- used in many aerodynamic studies.  - Wow.
如果幸运的话 我们可以在他的自然栖息地里看到他
If we're lucky, we'll see him in his natural habitat.
这是他的床
And this is his actual bed
他躺在这里思索生命最伟大的问题
where he lies and ponders life's greatest questions.
喂! 你在干吗?
Hey! What are you doing?
我在把你的名气兑现
I'm cashing in on your celebrity.
能给我签个名吗?
Can I have your autograph?
不能
Nope.
今天我的展示是...
And for show and tell today...
我的大哥哥!
my big brother!
呼!
Phew!
好久没见到你了
Oh! I haven't seen you in a while.
我整个人生都改变了 莱纳斯
My whole life has changed, Linus.
突然间 每个人都想跟我交朋友...
All of a sudden, everyone wants to be my friend...
然而 我没有真正改变
and yet, I haven't really changed.
他们是喜欢原本的我 还是他们想象中的我呢?
Do they like me for who I am, or for who they think I am?
他在那! 查理·布朗 我的国际象棋队需要你!
There he is! Charlie Brown, I need you on my chess team!
他没时间
He's got no time
浪费在无意义的游戏上 他得跟我走
for meaningless games. He's coming with me.
开机!
Roll sound!
- 场记  - 开拍!
- Speed.  - And, action!
你有时间帮我写我的读书报告吗?
Do you have time to help me write my book report?
周一就要交了
It's due on Monday.
周一? 报告周一就要交?
Monday? The report is due on Monday?
她周一就回来了! 我还没开始写呢!
She's back on Monday! I haven't even started yet!
有人知道玛茜在哪吗?
Does anyone know where Marcie is?
她跟薄荷·派蒂去溜冰了
She went skating with Peppermint Patty.
布朗先生 布朗先生!
Mr. Brown. Mr. Brown!
我的独家专访怎么办?
What about my exclusive?
停
Cut.
有哈克贝利费恩历险记...
There's Huckleberry Finn...
麦田里的守望者
Catcher in the Rye.
先生 我已经坐在这里好几个小时了
Sir, I've been sitting here for hours.
这些是有史以来最好的书
These are the greatest books of all time.
请选一本!
Please just pick one!
嗯 睡一觉再想吧 玛茜
Hmm. Let me sleep on it, Marcie.
没有睡觉的时间 先生
There's no time for sleeping, sir.
周一就截止了
It's due Monday.
白鲸记里的鲸鱼名
怪我搭上个认为莫比·迪克
Just my luck to get a partner that thinks Moby Dick
是曲棍球选手的搭档
was a hockey player.
玛茜? 你要去哪?
Marcie? Where are you going?
喂 老伙计
Hey, Chuck, old boy.
什么风把你吹来了?
What brings you down here?
我在找玛茜
I'm looking for Marcie.
我需要一些建议
I need some advice.
曲线球打不好吗? 强打不够力道吗?
Curveball not working for you? Slap shot not strong enough?
不 那些我都很擅长
No, I'm good with all that.
我得问问玛茜
I need to talk to Marcie about
怎么找到有史以来最棒的书
finding the greatest book of all time.
我可能可以帮得上你 伙计
I just might be able to help you there, Chuck.
玛茜刚刚读出了一长串很棒的小说
Marcie just read up a long list of great novels.
哈克贝利-什么的 拿着派的守望者
Huckleberry-something, Catcher with a Pie.
但她说最好的小说...
But, she said the greatest book of all time...
叫李奥的玩具手办...
is called Leo's Toy Store...
是一个叫沃伦...皮斯的老头写的
by some old guy called Warren... Piece.
李奥的玩具手办
Leo's Toy Store.
是的 就是那本 伙计
Yup. That's the one, Chuck.
谢谢你的建议
Thanks for the tip.
精气神不错 查克!
Love that hustle, Chuck!
有人知道在哪能找到李奥的玩具手办这本书吗?
Does anyone know where I can find Leo's Toy Store?
嘘
Shh.
李奥的玩具手办
Leo's Toy Store.
不是
Nope.
不 不是
No. No.
- 啊?  - 不是
- Huh?  - No.
在哪呢?
Hmm. Where is it?
他去了大人区
He's going into the grown-up's section.
那合法吗?
Is that legal?
查理? 我从没在这里见过你
Charles? I've never seen you in here before.
玛茜 谢天谢地我找到你了
Marcie, thank goodness I found you.
你能帮我找到一本李奥的玩具手办吗?
Can you help me find a copy of Leo's Toy Store?
你说的是"李奥的玩具手办"吗?
Did you say "Leo's Toy Store"?
是啊 薄荷·派蒂告诉我的
Yeah. Peppermint Patty told me
你说那是最棒的...
you said it was the greatest...
别说了 查理 跟我来
Stop right there, Charles. Come with me.
这就是你在找的书
This is what you're looking for.
列夫托尔斯泰听起来像李奥的玩具手办
列夫托尔斯泰的战争与和平
Leo Tolstoy's War and Peace.
哦
Oh.
天哪 这场战争有多久啊?
Yikes. How long was this war?
你确定要读这本书吗?
Are you sure that is the book you want to read?
我得提醒一下 查理
Might I remind you, Charles,
你只有一个周末的时间来完成读书报告
you only have the weekend to complete your report.
如果我想赢得金星星那我就不得不读
I have to if I'm going to win that gold star.
我没事
I'm okay.
鸿篇巨著
Big book.
你怎么拿回家呢 聪明人?
How are you gonna get it home, smarty-pants?
哈
Huh.
真聪明
Pretty smart.
我在说什么?
What am I saying?
老好人 查理·布朗
Good ol' Charlie Brown.
这才是成功人士的样子
Now there's a guy who's going places.
谢谢
Thanks.
呼
Phew.
惊喜!
Surprise!
生日快乐!
Happy Birthday!
谁请他来的?
Who invited him?
哈?
Huh?
战争与和平 第一页
War and Peace. Page one.
"啊 公爵 热那亚和卢加..."
"Eh bien, mon prince, so Genoa..."
喂 查理·布朗 出来玩!
Hey, Charlie Brown, come out and play!
- 歉 伙计们  - 噢!
- orry, guys.  - Aww!
周末谁还读书啊?
Who reads a book on the weekend?
- 反正我不读  - 好吧 我读到哪了?
- Not me.  - Okay. Where was I?
"从指挥官那牵走一匹马
"took a horse from a commander,
"饥寒交迫 衣衫褴褛..."
"and hungry and weary..."
"火枪的声音在远处回荡..."
"and the musketry fire sounded far away..."
"安德烈王子沉思着伟大的空虚...
"Prince Andrei mused on the unimportance of greatness...
"生命的空白 没人能够明白..."
"unimportance of life, which no one could understand..."
"昨天 还有前天..."
"and there was yesterday, and there was the day before..."
好了 演出结束了 请退场
Okay, show's over. Clear it out.
晚点还有演出吗?
Will there be a late show?
"并且承认我们感觉不出的依赖性"
"and to recognize a dependence we do not feel."
"全书完"
"The end."
我做到了
I did it.
嗯
Mmm-hmm.
都联系起来了
It's all coming together now.
这是我关于战争与和平的读书报告
Okay. This is my book report about War and Peace.
一 二 三 四 五 六 七 八 九
1,2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9.
开始有一场战争
First there was war.
然后就是和平
Then there was peace.
十 十一 十二 十三 十四 十五 十六 十七
10,11,12,13,14,15,16,17.
只剩九百八十三个字了
Only 983 words to go.
啊!
Ugh!
见鬼!
Rats!
没用的
This is no use.
我不如他们想象的那么聪明
I'm just not as smart as they think I am.
我不能让她失望
I can't let her down.
还有时间 你可以做到的
There's still time. You can do this.
你不可以现在就放弃她
You can't give up on her now.
九百九十八 九百九十九...
998, 999...
一千 写完了
1000. Finished.
醒醒 大哥哥!
Wake up, big brother!
今天有个庆祝你
Today's the big assembly
满分的大会
to celebrate your perfect score.
来看看!
Come see!
你又要干什么?
What are you up to now?
既然你是个大名人
Now that you're a big celebrity,
我们就要快点行动起来
we have to move fast.
我有T恤衫 帽子 杯子还有别的
I have shirts, hats, mugs, and more.
由于智商超群而产生的名气
The fame that comes with intellectual superiority
是很短暂的
can be very fleeting.
你必须趁还能够捞到钱的时候尽快兑现
You have to cash in while you can.
今天对于我们来说意义重大 大哥哥
Today is going to be a big day for us, big brother.
谢谢 欢迎再次光临
Thank you. Come again soon.
这都是为你准备的 查理·布朗
This is all for you, Charlie Brown.
你真的做到了
You've really made it.
就要来了
It's going to happen.
她终于要因为我做了一些
She's finally going to notice me
很棒的事而注意到我了
for doing something great.
嘿 查理·布朗
Charlie Brown.
我很不愿意承认 你这个木鱼脑袋...
I hate to admit it, you blockhead...
但是公众的意见让我相信
but public opinion leads me to believe,
这么多年...
that after all these years...
我可能对你有些误解
I may have been wrong about you.
这对我来说很不容易!
This is not easy for me!
我的整个世界都颠倒了!
My whole world has turned upside-down!
可以请查理·布朗到台上来吗?
Can I please have Charlie Brown come to the stage?
今天我很荣幸的向你们介绍...
It is my pleasure to present to you today...
本年度标准测试
this award for the highest achievement
的最高分数获得者
in this year's standardized testing.
但在我揭晓之前 学校公告
But before I do, the school proclamation.
"今天 你攀上了
"On this day, whereas you have upheld
"学术标准的最高峰"
"the highest of academic standards.
"从没人想过你能做到
"And whereas no one would have ever expected that of you.
"你是第一个得到
"And whereas you are the first
"满分的人
"to ever receive a perfect score.
"因此 校方决定
"Therefore, be it resolved
"将今天定为查理·布朗日
"that today is declared Charlie Brown Day.
"署名 奥兹玛老师"
"Signed, Miss Othmar."
那是我的大哥哥!
That's my big brother!
感觉怎么样 查理·布朗?
How about that, Charlie Brown?
你现在是学校的明星了!
You're the star of the school now!
祝贺你 查理
Congratulations, Charles.
让我把你的满分试卷给你
Let me present you with your perfect test.
哦 不 我肯定是把字签在错的卷子上了
Oh, no. I must have signed the wrong paper.
在我开始之前
Before I begin,
我想感谢所有你们给予我的支持
I'd like to thank all of you for your support.
你们都非常善良
You have all been so kind.
我不常会得到这种认可
It's not often that I get this sort of recognition.
但是 嗯...
But, um...
这是一个误会
there's been a mistake.
这不是我的试卷
This is not my test.
哈! 我就知道!
Ha! I knew it!
因为 我不能接受这项荣誉
Therefore, I cannot accept this honor.
哥哥和妹妹可以离婚么?
Can a brother and sister get a divorce?
我想这是属于薄荷·派蒂的
I think this belongs to Peppermint Patty.
她才是真的天才
She's the real genius.
你刚才做了一件非常值得称赞的事
That was a very admirable thing you just did,
查理·布朗
Charlie Brown.
某一刻我变成了英雄 下一刻就变成了一个罪人
One moment I'm the hero, the next I'm the goat.
也许在你上交你的读书报告后
Maybe things will go your way again
事情会再次朝对你有利的方向发展
after you hand in your book report.
我不太确定
I'm not so sure.
我为了完成它熬了整整一夜
I was up all night working on it
但我一个字都记不住了
and I can't remember a single word.
肯定不会像你想象的那么糟 查理·布朗
Surely it's not as bad as you think, Charlie Brown.
让我看看你写了些什么
Let me see what you wrote.
嗯 呃 哈
Hmm. Mmm-hmm. Huh.
查理·布朗 你对如此复杂小说的
Charlie Brown, the insight you bring
洞察力无可挑剔
to such a complex novel is beyond reproach.
以这份读书报告的质量
You two are sure to win the gold star
你们两个是注定要赢得金星星的
with a book report of this quality.
读书报告?
Book report?
我们要写读书报告吗?
Were we supposed to do a book report?
哦! 嗨 由于你当时不在...
Oh! Hi. In light of the fact that you were away...
查理·布朗主动承担了
Charlie Brown took it upon himself
为你们两人完成读书报告的重任
to complete the report for the both of you.
我不得不说 这是我读过的...
And I must say, this is one of the finest bits...
最好的分析文章
of literary analysis I have ever read.
啊!
Aaugh!
不 不 不!
No, no, no!
哦 真要命
Oh, good grief.
可能我们可以把它粘起来?
Maybe we can fix it?
第四章 诅咒你 红色男爵!
Chapter 4. Curse you, Red Baron!
呼!
Phew!
王牌飞行员无畏地
The Flying Ace set out across the hostile
朝着敌人的领地进发
countryside undeterred.
每当我感到真正的孤独时
Whenever I feel really alone,
我总会坐下来注视夜空
I just sit and stare into the night sky.
我总是觉得那些星星之中有一颗是我的...
I've always thought that one of those stars was my star...
每当这时
and at moments like this,
我就知道那里永远有我的星星
I know that my star will always be there for me.
就想一个令人舒服的声音在说, "不要放弃 孩子"
Like a comforting voice saying, "Don't give up, kid."
如果王牌飞行员是来营救菲菲的话
The Flying Ace had to return to the aerodrome...
他就必须返回机场...
if he was ever to rescue Fifi.
嗨
Hey.
嘘
Shh.
等我的提示
Wait for my cue.
我们想成功的话时间就至关重要
Timing is crucial if we're going to succeed.
他们不会想到我们会来
They'll never expect us.
盯住我 等我的信号
Eyes on me and wait for my signal.
圣诞节到了
Christmas time is here
开心又快乐
Happiness and cheer
好吧 查克 你家的小疯狗又来了
Yeah, Chuck, your crazy dog is over here again.
啊!
Aww!
抱歉 先生 你放过风筝吗?
Excuse me, mister. Have you ever flown a kite?
事实上 我想说...
Well, actually, let me just say that...
我有很多年放风筝的经验 但是我...
I have years of experience with kites, but I...
那太好了!
That's great!
哦! 好吧
Oh! Well, okay.
问题是 不是每个人都擅长放风筝
The thing is, flying a kite isn't for everyone.
只有特定的一类人才可以放好
It takes a certain type of person.
这有时会令人沮丧
It can frustrating at times.
风筝好像都有自己的想法
They tend to have a mind of their own.
但是只要有决心和投入
But with determination and dedication,
你也可以做到
you can make it happen.
真的吗?
Really?
给 你拿着绳子 站好
Here. You hold the string. Plant your feet.
重心向前 弯曲膝盖
Weight forward. Knees bent.
背挺直 抬头
Back straight. Head up.
记住 放轻松
And remember, keep it simple.
好
Okay.
我一说"开始" 你就尽可能快地跑
When I say "go," run as fast as you can.
往哪边 老师?
Which way, mister?
那边 现在 开始!
That way. Now, go!
我希望这个小家伙
I hope the little guy
不会灰心 史努比
doesn't get discouraged, Snoopy.
他还不清楚这会有多困难
He doesn't quite know how difficult this will be.
他可能要花费数年的时间
It may take him years
来达到我这种资历水平
to gain my level of experience.
罗马可不是一天...
It doesn't just happen over...
哈?
Huh?
呜呼! 飞起来了!
Woo-hoo! It's flying!
哇哦!
Wow!
谢谢你 老师 你真的很会放风筝
Thanks, mister. You sure know your kites.
你想试试吗?
Do you want to try?
你可以的!
You can do it!
别放弃!
Don't give up!
啊哈!
A-ha!
第七章 绝不放弃!
Chapter 7. Never give up!
王牌飞行员知道这将是
The Flying Ace knew this would be
他挽回一生所爱的最后机会
the last chance to save the love of his life.
哈?
Huh?
王牌飞行员与他一生挚爱
The Flying Ace returned to the aerodrome
返回了飞机场
with the love of his life.
如英雄般凯旋
He returned a hero.
"就这样 正如我们的英雄所见...
"And so, as our hero observed...
"他注定要再次面对
"he was destined to face
"臭名昭著的红男爵"
"the infamous Red Baron another day."
会飞的狗?
A dog that flies?
这是我读过的最蠢的东西了!
This is the dumbest thing I have ever read!
啊! 我染上狗细菌了!
Ugh! I got dog germs!
来啊 查理·布朗!
Come on, Charlie Brown!
今天要与众不同 开始了
Today calls for something special. Here we go.
嘿 各位
Hey, guys.
今天是学校最后一天!
It's the last day of school!
大哥哥 你能相信吗?
Well, big brother, can you believe it?
不用读书 写字 做算术了
No more reading, writing, arithmetic.
再也不用学习了!
No more learning ever!
你说什么呢?
What are you talking about?
这只是暑假开始而已
This is just the start of summer vacation.
你还要再读八年的初中
You have eight more years of grammar school.
四年高中
Four more years of high school.
- 八...  - 加上四年的大学
- Eight... - Plus four more years of college.
- 加四  - 还有另外一到四年的...
- Plus four.  - Add the one to an extra four...
这超过三十七年学啊!
That's over 37 years of school!
到时我就又秃又皱了
I'll be bald and wrinkly by then.
哇哦 快看啊!
Wow. Look at that!
那是史努比吗?
Is that Snoopy?
好幸运
Lucky.
好了 大家 听好了
Okay, everyone, listen up.
我知道这是学校最后一天了...
I know this is the last day of school...
耶!
Yay!
但首先 在离开之前...
But first, before we leave...
我们得为今年的
we need to finish picking our partners
暑假笔友项目选好搭档
for this year's summer pen-pal project.
我抽出一个名字
When I draw a name,
如果你想成为他的搭档 就站起来
stand if you want to be their partner.
开始咯 下一个名字是... 邋遢鬼乒乓!
Here we go. The next name is... Pigpen!
我愿意 一点泥巴没有害处
I will. A little dirt never hurt anyone.
施罗德
Schroeder.
我愿意!
I do!
我是说 我同意
I mean, I will.
查理·布朗
Charlie Brown.
我愿意
I will.
她愿意?
She will?
暑假咯!
Summertime!
嗨!
Hi!
查理·布朗 你去哪了?
Charlie Brown, where have you been?
今天是暑假第一天
It's the first day of summer.
你应该下来跟大家一起玩耍
You should be down there having fun with everyone else.
我没办法不去想 莱纳斯
I can't stop thinking about it, Linus.
在她目睹了今年
After all the humiliating disasters
所有丢人的灾难后...
she witnessed this year...
她为什么还选我?
why would she choose me?
她是在可怜我吗?
Was she feeling sorry for me?
我不想她是因为
I don't want her to choose me
可怜我才选我
just because she was feeling sorry for me.
我这点自尊还是有的
I have slightly more dignity than that.
查理·布朗...
Charlie Brown...
或许是时候想想那微小的可能了...
it might be time to consider the wild possibility...
你是个好人 大家喜欢你
that you're a good person and that people like you.
但你也知道 你永远不会
But, you know, you'll never
知道真正的答案 除非...
really know the answer, unless...
我过去问她!
I just go up and talk to her!
我一直都该听你的!
I should've listened to you all along!
哦! 我叫"查理" 呃 "查理·布朗"
Oh! "Charles." I mean, "Charlie Brown."
她不在?
She's not here?
正要去夏令营?
On her way to summer camp?
所以车还没离开学校?
So the bus hasn't left school yet?
但正要走了?
But it's about to leave?
对了 很高兴见到您 女士
And, by the way, it was a pleasure to meet you, ma'am.
查理·布朗!
Charlie Brown!
你个木鱼脑袋!
You blockhead!
呜! 好了!
Whoo! All right!
啊!
Aaugh!
耶!
Yay!
我怎么出去啊?
How do I get out of here?
好像全世界都在跟我作对
The whole world seems to be conspiring against me.
我这辈子就这么一次求你帮帮忙
I'm just asking for a little help for once in my life.
滚开!
Get out of here!
连你也欺负我!
Not you, too!
快看 是查理·布朗!!
Hey look, it's Charlie Brown!
查理·布朗在放风筝?
Charlie Brown is flying a kite?
查理·布朗在放风筝!
Charlie Brown is flying a kite!
哇哦! 查克把风筝放起来了
Wow! Chuck's got a kite in the air.
做得好 查克! 哇哦!
Way to go, Charles! Whoa!
哈?
Huh?
查理·布朗真的做到了!
Charlie Brown is really doing it!
他在放风筝!
He's flying a kite!
哇!
Whoa!
嗨 查理·布朗
Oh, hi, Charlie Brown.
你记得我的名字?
You remembered my name?
当然了
Of course I did.
在你走之前
Before you leave,
有件事我真的很想知道
there's something I really need to know.
为什么 在班上所有的孩子当中
Why, out of all the kids in our class,
你选了我做搭档?
would you want to be partners with me?
很简单啊
That's easy.
因为我看到了你的为人
Because I've seen the type of person you are.
一个不靠谱的 没有决心的失败者?
An insecure, wishy-washy failure?
你根本不是那样的
That's not who you are at all.
我喜欢你在才艺表演的时候
I like the compassion you showed
为妹妹展示出的同情
for your sister at the talent show.
表彰大会时你的诚实
The honesty you had at the assembly.
还有舞会的时候 你勇敢又好玩
And at the dance, you were brave, and funny.
窝心
Aww.
还有我不在的时候...
And what you did for me...
你帮我写读书报告 你太善良了
doing the book report while I was away, was so sweet of you.
所以我看着你的时候 我根本看不到失败者的影子
So when I look at you, I don't see a failure at all.
你有我钦佩的所有优点
You have all the qualities that I admire.
抱歉 我得走了
Sorry, I have to go now.
等下
Wait.
这应该是你的
I think this belongs to you.
谢谢 我到处在找它!
Thank you. I've been looking everywhere for this!
我会给你写信的 笔友
I'll write to you, pen-pal.
再见!
Bye!
他还好吧?
Is he okay?
嗷!
Aw!
此时此刻的查理·布朗
It must feel pretty great being
应该爽翻了吧
Charlie Brown right about now.
你做到了
You did it.
做得好 查克
Nice job, Chuck.
干得漂亮 查理!
Good job, Charles!
嘿 大哥哥!
Hey, big brother!
我作为你的妹妹很自豪
I'm proud to be your little sister.
闪开!
Out of my way!
不好
Uh-oh.
我必须告诉你一件事
I really need to tell you something,
你个木鱼脑袋
you blockhead.
你仍然充满惊喜
You're still full of surprises.
老好人查理·布朗!
Good ol' Charlie Brown!
# 什么也别想 #
# Don't think about it. #
# 只管舞动你的身体 #
# Just move your body #
# 听着音乐 唱 "哦耶哦" #
# Listen to the music. Sing, "Oh, yeah, oh" #
# 移动左脚 #
# Just move those left feet. #
# 来吧 疯狂起来 #
# Go ahead, get crazy. #
# 谁都可以 唱吧 "哦耶哦" #
# Anyone can do it. Sing, "Oh, yeah, oh" #
# 让世界看到你内心的烈火 #
# Show the world you got that fire. #
# 感受节奏不断变强 #
# Feel the rhythm getting louder. #
# 让世界知道你的能力 #
# Show the world what you can do. #
# 证明你可以跳舞 #
# Prove to them you got the moves. #
# 我不知道你是怎样 但跳舞的时候 #
# I don't know about you, but I feel better #
# 我感觉好了许多 #
# when I'm dancing. #
# 耶 耶 #
# Yeah, yeah. #
# 跳舞的时候 我感觉好了许多 #
# I'm better when I'm dancing. #
# 耶 耶 #
# Yeah, yeah. #
查理·布朗
Charlie Brown.
哦 查理·布朗
Oh, Charlie Brown.
我拿着橄榄球你来踢
I'll hold the football and you kick it.
你说你会拿着它 但你真正的意思是...
You say you'll hold it, but what you really mean is...
你会把它拿走 这样我会仰面摔倒
you'll pull it away, and I'll land on my back
摔死自己
and I'll kill myself.
但我觉得真的开始了解你了
But I feel I have really come to know you.
我现在知道你友好
I now understand that you are kind,
有同情 勇敢 幽默
compassionate, brave, and funny.
没有人会把橄榄球从这样一个人
No one would pull a football away
身边拿走的
from a person with all those qualities.
她说得对
She's right.
我也绝不会把球从这样一个人
I would never pull the ball away
身边拿走的
from someone with all those qualities.
我要把这个球踢到月球上
I'm gonna kick this ball all the way to the moon.
还有容易上当 我忘了说"容易上当"了
And gullible. I forgot to mention "gullible."
# 跳舞的时候 我感觉好多了 #
# I feel better when I'm dancing. #
# 耶 耶 #
# Yeah, yeah. #
# 跳舞的时候 我感觉好多了 #
# I'm better when I'm dancing. #
# 耶 耶 #
# Yeah, yeah. #
# 我们可以一起跳 #
# Oh, we can do this together. #
# 我打赌你跳舞时感觉更好 #
# I bet you feel better when you're dancing. #
# 耶 耶 #
# Yeah, yeah #
# 当你抛下拘束 #
# When you finally let go #
# 当你唱起独奏 #
# and you sing that solo. #
# 因为你听着音乐 唱着"哦 耶 哦" #
# 'Cause you listen to the music. Sing, "Oh, yeah, oh" #
# 因为你自信 宝贝 #
# 'Cause you're confident, babe #
# 你摇摆起臀部 #
# And you make your hips sway #
# 我们知道你可以 唱吧"哦 耶 哦" #
# We knew that you could do it. Sing, "Oh, yeah, oh" #
# 让世界看到你内心的烈火 #
# Show the world you got that fire #
# 感受节奏不断变强 #
# Feel the rhythm getting louder #
# 让世界知道你的能力 #
# Show the world what you can do #
给我们的英雄来圈啤酒 敬王牌飞行员!
A round of root beers for our hero, the Flying Ace!
- 万岁万万岁!  - 万岁!
- Hip-hip hooray!  - Hooray!
万岁万万岁! 万岁万万岁!
Hip-hip hooray! Hip-hip hooray!
去死吧 红伯爵!
# 我不要担心所有的问题 #
# I ain't trying to think about all my problems #
# 我要活在当下 #
# I'm living now #
# 享受当下 #
# 我不会坐着担心未来 #
# I can't sit and worry about the future #
# 我要活在当下 #
# I'm living now #
# 活在当下啊 #
# Said I'm living now #
# 如果感到快乐 #
# So put your hands up #
# 你就举起双手 #
# if you feel like having a good time #
# 如果无忧无虑 #
# Put your hands up #
# 你就举起双手 #
# If you got no cares at all #
# 如果明天不上班 #
# Raise your cups #
# 就举杯庆祝 #
# If you got no work tomorrow #
# 如果你准备好了享乐 #
# Put your hands up #
# 就举起双手 #
# If you're ready to have some fun #
# 来吧 唱起来 #
# Come on, sing it #
# 哦 活着的感觉真好 #
# Oh, it feels so good to be alive #
# 感觉好极了吧 来吧 #
# Don't it feel good, come on #
# 哦 活着的感觉真好 #
# Oh, it feels so good to be alive #
# 来吧 #
# Come on #
# 我要每天醒来都像迎接圣诞 #
# I'm gonna wake up every day like it's Christmas #
# 我要庆祝活着的人生 #
# I'm gonna celebrate this life I'm living #
# 从现在开始 #
# From now on #
# 我要每天告诉妈妈我爱她 #
# I'm gonna tell my mother every day I love her #
# 感谢她是如此好的妈妈 #
# And tell her thanks for being such a good mother #
# 从现在开始 #
# From now on #
# 来吧 #
# Come on #
# 如果感到快乐 #
# So put your hands up #
# 你就举起手 #
# if you feel like having a good time #
# 如果无忧无虑 #
# Put your hands up #
# 你就举起手 #
# If you got no cares at all #
# 如果明天不上班 #
# Raise your cups #
# 就举杯庆祝 #
# If you got no work tomorrow #
# 如果你准备好了享乐 #
# Put your hands up #
# 就举起双手 #
# If you're ready to have some fun #
# 来吧 唱起来 #
# Come on, sing it #
# 哦 活着的感觉真好 #
# Oh, it feels so good to be alive #
# 没错 #
# Yes, it does #
# 感觉真好 不是吗 #
# It feels good, don't it #
# 在这短暂的时刻享受生活? #
# Living your life in this quick moment? #
# 从没想过它会结束 但我要说 #
# And you never ever think it's gonna go away, but I'll say #
# 我知道有天你会醒来说 #
# I know you'll wake up one day and say #
# 我还有事情要做 #
# Yeah, I got things to do #
# 我还有山要撼动 #
# Yeah, I got mountains to move #
# 关键不是这有多悲伤 #
# And it ain't about how sad it could be #
# 而是会多么美好 #
# It's about how good it should be #
# 来吧 唱起来 #
# Come on, sing #
# 感觉真好 不是吗? 感觉真好 不是吗? #
# It feels good, don't it? It feels good, don't it? #
# 生命只有一次 活在当下 #
# You only got one life, live in the moment #
# 感觉真好 不是吗? 感觉真好 不是吗? #
# It feels good, don't it? It feels good, don't it? #
# 生命只有一次 活在当下 #
# You only got one life, live in the moment #
# 感觉真好 不是吗? 感觉真好 不是吗? #
# It feels good, don't it? It feels good, don't it? #
# 生命只有一次 活在当下 #
# You only got one life, live in the moment #
# 感觉真好 不是吗? 感觉真好 不是吗? #
# It feels good, don't it? It feels good, don't it? #
# 生命只有一次 #
# You only got one life #
# 来吧 唱起来 #
# Come on, sing it #
# 哦 活着的感觉真好 #
# Oh, it feels so good to be alive #
# 一切都会很好 来吧 #
# All will feel good, come on #
# 哦 这感觉真好 #
# Oh, it feels so good #
# 哦 活着的感觉真好 #
# Oh, it feels so good to be alive #
# 感觉真好不是吗 #
# Don't it feel good? #
# 哦 活着的感觉真好 #
# Oh, it feels so good to be alive #
# 来吧 唱起来 #
# Come on, sing it #
# 感觉真好 不是吗? 感觉真好 不是吗? #
# It feels good, don't it? It feels good, don't it? #
# 生命只有一次 活在当下 #
# You only got one life, live in the moment #
# 感觉真好 不是吗? 感觉真好 不是吗? #
# It feels good, don't it? It feels good, don't it? #
# 生命只有一次 活在当下 #
# You only got one life, live in the moment #
# 哦 活着的感觉真好 #
# Oh, it feels so good to be alive #
支持我们，欢迎购买VIP移除所有广告，具体：www.OpenSubtitles.org